<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<reference id="reconciliation-faqs">
  <title>Product FAQs</title>
  <shortdesc>Learn about frequently asked questions regarding the product.</shortdesc>
  <body>
    <table>
      <tgroup cols="2">
        <colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1*"/>
        <colspec colname="c2" colwidth="3*"/>
        <thead>
          <row>
            <entry>Question</entry>
            <entry>Answer</entry>
          </row>
        </thead>
        <tbody>
          <row>
            <entry>What is reconciliation?</entry>
            <entry>Reconciliation is the process of reviewing and comparing Title IV aid (grants, loans, and campus-based aid) recorded on Department of Education (ED) systems using internal records. You must resolve discrepancies, document reasons for any remaining cash balances, and retain reconciliation documentation for auditing purposes. Your offices should reconcile records before reconciling to ED.
</entry>
          </row>
          <row>
            <entry>How often is reconciliation necessary?</entry>
            <entry>Campus-based aid and Direct Loan require monthly reconciliation. The best practice is to reconcile each fund source monthly.</entry>
          </row>
          <row>
            <entry>Is it safe to upload my COD and SIS files into the product?</entry>
            <entry>Yes, it is safe. No personal identification information (PII) is retained in the system. After the process runs, all PII is deleted from the servers.</entry>
          </row>
          <row>
            <entry>How long do you store data?</entry>
            <entry>Report results are available for 90 days on the website. Users can run reports as often as needed.</entry>
          </row>
          <row>
            <entry>How can files be exported to Excel and saved locally?</entry>
            <entry>Matching result reports can be exported as CSV files and opened in Excel. Users can save the exported files to their local drive for further analysis and record-keeping.</entry>
          </row>
        </tbody>
      </tgroup>
    </table>
  </body>
</reference>
